<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<topics>
  <topic number="1">
    <title>wordpress</title>
    <description>General information about the publishing platform wordpress.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant are things like what is wordpress, how it works, how to install and use it. Irrelevant are wordpress driven sites, wordpress management sites. </narrative>
    <group>uk-ir-1</group>
    <university>Universität Kassel</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_14_591149136,msmarco_v2.1_doc_14_591493828,msmarco_v2.1_doc_30_42814983</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_07_1077269072,msmarco_v2.1_doc_32_514402783,msmarco_v2.1_doc_00_549094198</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="2">
    <title>remote work productivity</title>
    <description>How does remote work impact employee productivity, and what factors influence productivity in remote work environments?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant Documents must include studies or reports on the effects of remote work on the productifity of employees in corporate or knowledge-based industries. This includes information on factors such as work environment, use of technology, communication methods, flexibility, and work-life balance. Documents that focus solely on other forms of work or industries are not relevant.</narrative>
    <group>Guugel</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_40_741420104,msmarco_v2.1_doc_27_637976652</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_31_1296492155,msmarco_v2.1_doc_40_1056364002</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="3">
    <title>st link 2</title>
    <description>A user wants to build an IoT sensor based on an STM32 microchip. To program this microchip, they are looking to buy a compatible programmer/debugger kit, named “ST-Link V2”. The user is also interested in the wiring of the debugger.</description>
    <narrative>Documents that describe where to buy an ST-Link V2 debugger, or documents describing how to set up the wiring to STM32 microchips for programming with the ST-Link V2.
Documents about other microchips (e.g., ESP32), about different ways to program microchips, or other debugger devices are irrelevant. Moreover, documents about the previous version of the ST-Link (V1) are not relevant.</narrative>
    <group>Tutors</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_09_807623049,msmarco_v2.1_doc_31_971327103,msmarco_v2.1_doc_39_1112560670</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_2348396879,msmarco_v2.1_doc_28_1199872210,msmarco_v2.1_doc_31_969815887</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="4">
    <title>Triathlon Club</title>
    <description>Are there local sports clubs for triathlon, when are associated events and how can you join? </description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents would include information on triathlon clubs, membership information, upcoming events and training times (not geographically limited). Also relevant could be information on clubs, events, etc. exclusive for cycling, running or swimming. Not relevant documents include old news articles on triathlon events in Jena, product information on triathlon clothing, historical events connecting Jena to triathlon or general information/forums on the sport itself.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_00_1082512799,msmarco_v2.1_doc_55_1181515248,msmarco_v2.1_doc_55_1181527839</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_10_150652524,msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_3232669835</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="5">
    <title>1984</title>
    <description>What is George Orwells Novel 1984 about? who wrote 1984? why is 1984 so controversial? where can i buy or access 1984?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant: An outline, summary or analysis of 1984; Bookstores which sell the novel or an audiobook version. Irrelevant: Events that took place in the year of 1984.</narrative>
    <group>Golden Retrieval</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_21_274003411,msmarco_v2.1_doc_06_689266876,msmarco_v2.1_doc_41_1257042930</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_1138217712,msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_1139321971,msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_1138761690</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="6">
    <title>Waltz</title>
    <description>What are the steps to a waltz and what can I dance it to?</description>
    <narrative>Documents about the steps and characteristics of the dance and music should be considered most important. The History of the dance should be considered less relevant and Names should not be considered relevant at all.</narrative>
    <group>Zero Latency</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_07_812301728,msmarco_v2.1_doc_06_1721543966,msmarco_v2.1_doc_05_809727723</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_03_1470893658,msmarco_v2.1_doc_09_1594250375,msmarco_v2.1_doc_05_809272938</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="7">
    <title>Test</title>
    <description>What are the methods available for testing internet speed, and how do they work? What are the main factors affecting internet speed test results, and how can users interpret their outcomes?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents must include information on different methods or tools available to test internet speed, such as web-based speed tests, apps, or hardware solutions. Relevant details may include explanations of the parameters measured in a speed test (such as download/upload speed, latency, jitter), factors affecting speed (such as network congestion, device limitations), and guidelines for interpreting results. Technical breakdowns, comparisons of speed test providers, and insights into factors that can cause variation in test results are also relevant.

Irrelevant documents include general information on internet services, broadband pricing, unrelated networking concepts, or content focused on internet speed improvement tips without directly addressing speed testing methods or interpretations.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_2701526052,msmarco_v2.1_doc_29_973994362,msmarco_v2.1_doc_47_113674761</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_2921151683,msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_2701895499,msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_2403580131</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="8">
    <title>conTeXt latex compare</title>
    <description>What are the differences between LaTeX and ConTeXt and which are the pros and cons regarding them. The situation might be, that the user is not sure which to use for a project.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents are documents comparing both LaTeX and ConTeXt as well as listing their pros and cons. Not relevant are documents only focusing on one of these languages (which may happen because LaTeX is more present). Even more irrelevant are documents which interpret ConTeXt as the noun "context", therefore drifting into totally different subjects. (also LaTeX as the material latex) </narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_29_980132973</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_30_1559864554,msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_938115858,msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_554202046</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="9">
    <title>spiders sweden</title>
    <description>Information about spiders in Sweden. Say you want to prepare for holiday in Sweden and want to know everything about them. Are they common, dangerous, large, or sparse, small and hideous?</description>
    <narrative>Irrelevant is spiders in general (without Sweden) or Swedish animals without spiders. The focus lies on natural occurring spider population, not in a zoo or aquarium (like skansen). Also unimportant is Arachnological intellectuals who are Swedish (Carl Alexander Clerck) or main articles about fossils that contain spiders (sea spider fossil found in sweden) or folklore (Legend of the christmas spider) or spider man (superhero) in sweden. Irrelevant is also birds located in sweden, eating spiders (although that implies that there are indeed spiders in Sweden).
Relevant is spiders that occur in Sweden with information about their dangers and how common they are. Relevant is also that there aren't spiders in Sweden.</narrative>
    <group>Unkn0wnEngine</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_00_308352559,msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_465138427</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_190108886,msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_1951859106,msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_2685472554</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="10">
    <title>how to write an scientific assignment</title>
    <description>Was muss man beim Verfassen einer wissenschaftlichen Hausarbeit beachten und wie geht man dabei am besten vor?</description>
    <narrative>Relevante Dokumente müssen sich auf das Verfassen wissenschaftlicher Hausarbeiten, wie an Universitäten üblich, beziehen. Sie sollten Informationen über Anforderungen an solche Hausarbeiten, Strategien zum Verfassen solcher Hausarbeiten und Tipps, die das Verfassen erleichtern, enthalten. Irrelevant sind alle Dokumente, die sich auf Hausarbeiten beziehen, die keinen wissenschaftlichen Anspruch haben oder sich auf andere Bereiche als dem Verfassen einer Hausarbeit beziehen.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_33_594950851,msmarco_v2.1_doc_53_450100889,msmarco_v2.1_doc_24_1302189116</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_12_21168282,msmarco_v2.1_doc_41_656558495</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="11">
    <title>Buy Blush</title>
    <description>I wanted to search for information about blush, a cosmetic product used to add color to the cheeks.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents:
Product pages with information and reviews on Blush.
Blush selection and application guides.
E-commerce pages with purchase options for Blush.
Non-relevant documents:
Articles about unrelated products (e.g. Kent-Mango).
Wikipedia pages or other texts that use “blush” in a different context (e.g. as a sentiment).
Articles on other cosmetic products that do not deal with blush.
Documents are only relevant if they refer to blush as a cosmetic product.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_32_1313059480</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_2441865328,msmarco_v2.1_doc_57_1503297333,msmarco_v2.1_doc_54_877064632</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="12">
    <title>scrum principles</title>
    <description>What are the main principles of SCRUM, containing process, events and roles?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents should include a description of the Scrum process, roles, and events, which are the core principles of Scrum. The process refers to the rhythm of the sprints. The roles include the Product Owner, Development Team, Management, Scrum Master, and Customer. The events consist of Daily Scrums, Sprint Reviews, Sprint Retrospectives, and Sprint Planning.
Instead of the word "principles" also "artifacts" could be accepted.
Not relevant are documents about technical details, alternatives of scrum or personal opinions on scrum.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_56_195927649,msmarco_v2.1_doc_57_60734702,msmarco_v2.1_doc_33_669894206</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_03_1286753018,msmarco_v2.1_doc_26_748655295,msmarco_v2.1_doc_52_214700070</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="13">
    <title>bicycle repair jena</title>
    <description>a shop or something like that to repair my bike. and located in Jena</description>
    <narrative>
relevant document would ideally include listings for bike repair shops in Jena,germany</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos> </relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_53_232998386,msmarco_v2.1_doc_43_933095398</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="14">
    <title>Muscle Gain</title>
    <description>information, data and media on how, where and when to gain muscles, as well as biological aspects of this process.</description>
    <narrative>videos, files and websites about studies on hypertrophy, strength training routines, protein intake, and recovery techniques. Articles solely about weight loss, cardiovascular fitness, or body toning without an emphasis on building muscle mass would be irrelevant. Misinterpretations like focusing on fat loss instead of muscle growth, should also be labeled irrelevant.</narrative>
    <group>Guugel</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_360388659,msmarco_v2.1_doc_46_1041138799,msmarco_v2.1_doc_06_604939385</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_57_904824464,msmarco_v2.1_doc_28_437730121,msmarco_v2.1_doc_01_396060200</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="15">
    <title>arabic food recipes</title>
    <description>A collection of popular Arabic food recipes that guides users on how to cook traditional Arabic dishes.</description>
    <narrative>Documents should include lists of the most popular Arabic food recipes, complete with step-by-step cooking instructions, ingredient lists, and brief descriptions of each dish. These resources are relevant because they allow users to explore, learn, and cook authentic Arabic cuisine.

What is irrelevant in these documents are any discussions on political topics related to Arabic cuisine or any unrelated historical or cultural conflicts. The focus should remain exclusively on the culinary aspects, such as recipes, ingredients, techniques, and cooking traditions.</narrative>
    <group>Gruppe 5</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_04_1152546079,msmarco_v2.1_doc_05_402570237</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_2276869673,msmarco_v2.1_doc_20_177807776</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="16">
    <title>Mental health impacts of social media </title>
    <description>What effects can social media have on mental health?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents must include details of psychological effects on the mental health or the behavior of social media users. The effects can either be positiv or negative.  
The mechanisms of how social media works are irrelevant</narrative>
    <group>Zero Latency</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos> </relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos/>
  </topic>
  <topic number="17">
    <title>Addictions</title>
    <description>What kind of harmful addictions are there and how can they be treated?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents must include information about addictions, those include physical addictions and psychological addictions. Relevant are informations about general informations about addictions, the causes of addiction, the signs of addiction and different treatment methods for certain addictions as well as methods to avoid getting addicted.

Not relevant are documents which use the word addiction or addictive as an acronym for good, for example in advertising.</narrative>
    <group>Guugel </group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_41_1654746135,msmarco_v2.1_doc_46_840761647,msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_284625871</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_45_957290655</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="18">
    <title>c string handling</title>
    <description>What are the characteristics and the common usage of strings in the programming language C?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents must explain what a string in the programming language c is, how it can be used, and further technical details about the usage.
Also, there should be a list of common functions that operate on strings.
Irrelevant documents are such containing information about underwear (c strings) and music (string of an instrument).</narrative>
    <group>suchMASCHINEN</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_2654300274</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_56_174065273,msmarco_v2.1_doc_56_171888109</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="19">
    <title>Unicode table characters</title>
    <description>What characters can be used to build tables? Especially focus on the Box Drawing Unicode block and avoid other blocks that are displayed as tables.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents include characters that can be used for tables e.g. on the CLI. Irrelevant are documents that contain tables of other characters.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_30_1555120184,msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_2486629328,msmarco_v2.1_doc_11_931363152</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_2621207293,msmarco_v2.1_doc_11_932188470,msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_3087092020</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="20">
    <title>Interrail ticket</title>
    <description>What kind of different Interrail/Eurrail tickets and passes are there and where can you buy them?</description>
    <narrative>Must include how Interrail ticket can be used for riding trains inside Europe and how much various tickets cost. Relevant details include information about different offers and how long they allow you to ride by train, where and how to buy the ticket, which citizens qualify for the ticket and which European train companies take part in the ticket. Not relevant are different tickets.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_22_1088759001,msmarco_v2.1_doc_44_467859681,msmarco_v2.1_doc_51_86651040</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_51_86651040,msmarco_v2.1_doc_44_920496879,msmarco_v2.1_doc_55_210372403</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="21">
    <title>godot game engine</title>
    <description>The title is about a game engine named Godot, which is used for game development.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents are all docs about godot game engine, for example tutorials, Godot official docs, godot github page, discussion forums about godot game engine, docs that compare godot game engine with other game engine, etc.
Documents about other game engines where they do not mention godot are not relevant!
Documents about other engines like car engines are not relevant.
Documents about general game development are not relevant.
</narrative>
    <group>Keine Name bisher :( </group>
    <university>Universität Kassel</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_1203090464,msmarco_v2.1_doc_20_1213543996,msmarco_v2.1_doc_28_1595042393</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_2157949596,msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_1029128287,msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_1980111610</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="22">
    <title>meat production</title>
    <description>How is meat produced? What are the ingredients and how are they processed?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant Documents should include documentation on farming conditions, livestock breeding, butchering or additional ingredients used in meat. Details schould be about different farming methods and differences beetween fresh and conserved meat. The documents should also include informations about the jobs that are needed to produce meat. Not relevant are Shopping offers for meat, job offers in the industry or recipes with meat.</narrative>
    <group>Golden Retrieval</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_03_742229918</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_45_1210630094</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="23">
    <title>neural processing unit</title>
    <description>What are neural processing units and what's their application.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents describe the general idea of how it works, explaining the mathematical operation and architecture, and why neural processing units are integrated in modern hardware. Relevant documents may also describe a processor that has the same architecture and mathematical operation, but is label by another name. Irrelevant documents describe only a neural network, i.e. no information is provided about the processor itself, or anything related to the biological neurons.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_22_1185340258,msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_1043649314,msmarco_v2.1_doc_14_501077118</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_38_1422005410,msmarco_v2.1_doc_01_402631004,msmarco_v2.1_doc_02_132277585</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="24">
    <title>Virtual Reality in Medical Training</title>
    <description>How is virtual reality (VR) technology used in medical education and training, and what are its benefits?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents must discuss the application of virtual reality in medical training environments. Relevant details include descriptions of VR-based training programs, the types of medical procedures or skills taught through VR, the benefits of using VR over traditional training methods, and data on the effectiveness or limitations of VR training. Relevant documents may also discuss ethical considerations, costs, and technological challenges associated with VR in medical education. Documents are irrelevant if they focus solely on VR applications outside of medical training, such as VR in gaming, entertainment, or other non-medical educational contexts. Also irrelevant are documents that only mention VR in passing without discussing its specific applications, benefits, or challenges in medical training.</narrative>
    <group>Suchende Schillerlinge</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_3310501,msmarco_v2.1_doc_42_886023235</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_44_604034439</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="25">
    <title>sleep problems solution </title>
    <description>A targeted search is made for ways or advice to overcome sleep disorders. The aim is to find strategies or solutions that will help you fall asleep more quickly.</description>
    <narrative>relevant document : Self-help article on improving sleep not relevant : Documentation about a health problem other than a sleep disorder</narrative>
    <group>Die Datenjäger</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos> </relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos/>
  </topic>
  <topic number="26">
    <title>Moon</title>
    <description>Information and data about the celestial body "Moon" that orbits the Earth.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant Documents include data and trivia about the Moon. This includes the lunar cycle, orbital characteristics, physical characteristics, solar and lunar eclipse, effect on earth,hHistory of exploration and human presence as well as cultural articles including the Moon. Moons other than Earth's Moon are irrelevant.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_2894220115,msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_285974931</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_1113751481,msmarco_v2.1_doc_18_1339010247,msmarco_v2.1_doc_16_2094803738</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="27">
    <title>training stress score</title>
    <description>What is the training stress score, i.e. how is it defined and calculated and what is it intended to measure?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant include details about the calculation of the training stress score metric invented by TrainingPeaks. This includes the prerequisites needed for calculating it. Also relevant is information about the goals of the metric, i.e. what it is intended to measure. Not relevant are documents not relevant to this exact metric (like TRIMP). Irrelevant in particular are documents about stress not related to endurance training (like those about psychological stress).</narrative>
    <group>suchMASCHINEN</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_14_1537185502</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_53_430225065,msmarco_v2.1_doc_19_723601450</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="28">
    <title>3D Printing</title>
    <description>An explanation of what 3D printing is and its applications (manufacturing, prototyping, medical applications, consumer products). Information about different 3D printing methods (FDM, SLA, SLS) as well as the materials one can use for printing (plastics, metals, ceramics). Hardware and Software involved in 3D printing.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents would provide overviews of 3D printing technology, step-by-step guides on how to get started with 3D printing, examples showcasing successful and failed 3D prints as well as a website providing on-demand 3D printing services.
Irrelevant are documents that focus on related but distinct technologies like 2D printing, CNC machining, or general additive manufacturing without specifically addressing 3D printing. 
</narrative>
    <group>Guugel</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_00_23277996,msmarco_v2.1_doc_22_491224802</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_31_1363891994</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="29">
    <title>renewable energy types</title>
    <description>What are the different types of renewable energy, how do they work and what are their benefits?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents must contain details on different types of renewable energy. Relevant details include the source of the energy, explanations of how the technologies work and their benefits compared to other energy sources. Documents focussing on energy sources that are non-renewable are not relevant.</narrative>
    <group/>
    <university/>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_48_1098286366,msmarco_v2.1_doc_39_425602624</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_02_1257864630,msmarco_v2.1_doc_28_782802451</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="30">
    <title>Malware Development using indirect System Call</title>
    <description>This topic explores the use of indirect system calls in malware development, a technique increasingly employed by attackers to bypass security mechanisms and detection systems. Unlike direct system calls, which are straightforward and more easily monitored by security tools, indirect system calls use alternative methods (such as API redirection or syscall stubs) to achieve similar functionality in a stealthier way. This allows malware to perform malicious actions while evading detection. Understanding this technique is crucial for cybersecurity professionals working on malware analysis and defense strategies, as it sheds light on a sophisticated method of obfuscation used in modern malware to avoid detection by anti-virus software and endpoint protection solutions.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents for this topic would include technical analyses, research papers, and security blogs that discuss the implementation, detection, and mitigation of indirect system calls in malware. Documents detailing how malware authors use indirect system calls to evade detection, case studies of malware families known to use this technique, and methods for detecting indirect system calls in security monitoring would also be pertinent. Additionally, any resources covering the technical methods used to implement indirect system calls, such as inline hooks, API unhooking, or system call stubs, would be highly relevant.

Documents not relevant to this topic would include general discussions of system calls that do not address the concept of indirect system calls or malware evasion techniques. Introductory material on system calls without a security or malware focus, as well as discussions on general software engineering practices unrelated to malware or cybersecurity, would also be irrelevant. Additionally, any document that discusses indirect system calls without a focus on malicious uses would not be considered relevant.</narrative>
    <group>Unkn0wnEngine</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_05_1754468371</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_1953703347,msmarco_v2.1_doc_51_1793975314,msmarco_v2.1_doc_25_943603137</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="31">
    <title>Best Machine Learning Algorithms for Real Applications</title>
    <description>Data scientists and machine learning engineers often need to decide which algorithm or model architecture best suits their use case. They might search for “best ML algorithms for image recognition” or “NLP model benchmarking”. This need arises when they are selecting or fine-tuning models and want to understand how different algorithms perform across datasets and applications. Users are looking for resources that provide comparative benchmarks, real-world application insights, and case studies that reveal the strengths and weaknesses of different models.</description>
    <narrative>Relevant Documents: These would include research papers, technical reports, case studies, and industry blogs with quantitative comparisons, application case studies, or benchmarking results. Relevant documents may also include discussions on model performance across various metrics (accuracy, latency, computational cost, etc.).

Non-Relevant Documents: General ML tutorials that lack specific performance insights, blog posts without data-driven analysis, or content focusing on algorithm theory without practical comparisons would be less relevant. For instance, a general overview of deep learning techniques without any application-focused comparisons would not meet the information need.</narrative>
    <group>Zero Latency</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_56_289616446,msmarco_v2.1_doc_44_1578564781</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_50_600979409,msmarco_v2.1_doc_21_180322041</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
  <topic number="32">
    <title>Storage Engines</title>
    <description>What are storage engines, how do they function, and what are their roles in managing data? What are the differences among popular storage engines, and how are they selected for specific applications?</description>
    <narrative>Relevant documents must include detailed information about different types of storage engines, such as how they work, their use cases, and their efficiency in managing and retrieving data. Descriptions should cover popular storage engines (e.g., InnoDB, MyISAM, RocksDB) and explain how they handle tasks like indexing, transactions, and concurrency. Information about the performance, scalability, and reliability of storage engines, along with factors influencing their selection in various applications, is also relevant. Documents may include comparisons of storage engines in terms of speed, memory usage, and compatibility with database systems, as well as any laws, standards, or best practices governing their implementation and usage.</narrative>
    <group>Suchende Schillerlinge</group>
    <university>Friedrich-Schiller-Universität Jena</university>
    <relevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_17_649405805,msmarco_v2.1_doc_15_1114104299,msmarco_v2.1_doc_44_98544961</relevant_docnos>
    <irrelevant_docnos>msmarco_v2.1_doc_43_517325445,msmarco_v2.1_doc_14_495497117,msmarco_v2.1_doc_27_1478761612</irrelevant_docnos>
  </topic>
</topics>
